linksroll.info 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy | Ready2Beat.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to **contact us**.

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected and how it is used.   

**Information collections:**

It is not mandatory to give all the personal information at time of user registration. We need just a valid e-mail address for further communication. All the information in Profile is not mandatory in any way. We don't verify such personal information or photographs. We check the url of the link submitted by automatic scripts.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, this site makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

This site does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

It is widely used on internet and generally doesn't make any harm to user’s information.  
Please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/>.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. 

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -[ ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include  
Google Adsense and  
Chitika.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on this site send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

Our site has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Out site's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

**Security of your information** : 

Our user accounts are password protected. We or our employee don't use such information for any personal or public use. We don't share, sell, broadcast or delete personal information of our users. We advice our users to keep their account secure with strong password. Don't share your password on the internet. You may request deletion of your ready2beat account by e-mailing us at **contact-AT-ready2beat-dot-com**

**Privacy policy Limitation** : 

Our Privacy policy is only limited within our website. When you click on story link and leave our website, it will not include you in our policy.

Also we can change our privacy policy at any time without any notice. However we will announce here the last date of update.
